[{"answer": "Well, he didn't need a -- any hand gun to kill to murder his wife and leave the poor baby as an orphan.", "docId": "121203pmt", "aSentId": 42, "question": "Why did Jovan Belcher need a high-powered hand gun?", "qSentId": 41}, {"answer": "So what you mean -- so you call it high powered handgun by which you mean a normal handgun and I don't know why he owned a handgun.", "docId": "121203pmt", "aSentId": 52, "question": "Well, I'm assuming most hand guns are high powered, right?", "qSentId": 51}, {"answer": "Right.", "docId": "121203pmt", "aSentId": 101, "question": "At what point do you say in America, enough guns, actually what we need to do is reduce the number of guns?", "qSentId": 100}, {"answer": "Well, you see, you want to confiscate all guns in the United States.", "docId": "121203pmt", "aSentId": 105, "question": "Why don't we try 300 million?", "qSentId": 104}, {"answer": "It's mind-boggling to me.", "docId": "121203pmt", "aSentId": 179, "question": "What is your take on it?", "qSentId": 178}, {"answer": "Well, again, there's a time and a place.", "docId": "121203pmt", "aSentId": 198, "question": "What is your view of what he said and his right to say it?", "qSentId": 197}, {"answer": "Well, they ought to be dealing with this on the up-and-up instead of dealing the way they are.", "docId": "121203pmt", "aSentId": 216, "question": "Short of bringing you out of retirement, what should they be doing?", "qSentId": 215}, {"answer": "Now you're talking about some good football there, buddy.", "docId": "121203pmt", "aSentId": 228, "question": "Confident?", "qSentId": 227}, {"answer": "No, it's not.", "docId": "121203pmt", "aSentId": 273, "question": "The law is being changed to ensure that whoever the firstborn child is, boy or girl, will automatically become king or queen, but it's not actually a done deal yet, is it?", "qSentId": 272}, {"answer": "Well, like you say, if this legislation comes into play, which I suspect it will ahead of the birth, then yes, if the firstborn, the first twin to birth is a girl, then she will take precedence over either the sister or the brother.", "docId": "121203pmt", "aSentId": 285, "question": "Is it literally the first one out is the heir?", "qSentId": 284}, {"answer": "It is worse than just typical morning sickness.", "docId": "121203pmt", "aSentId": 307, "question": "People call it acute morning sickness or whatever, but it's a bit worse than that, isn't it?", "qSentId": 306}, {"answer": "Well, it does increase the possible risk of having a baby prematurely, although if you look across the board, most babies are born perfectly healthy so it's a small increase in that sort of condition but typically if it's going to be treated well and again, lasting just a few weeks, then everything should go pretty well after that.", "docId": "121203pmt", "aSentId": 320, "question": "Does it increase the potential risk of a miscarriage?", "qSentId": 319}, {"answer": "Well, you know, I think a lot of people are certainly looking that way.", "docId": "121203pmt", "aSentId": 325, "question": "And do you see again -- I know you've done so much on this, but do you see a potential parallel here with him?", "qSentId": 324}, {"answer": "Well, it's not clear that both sides know.", "docId": "121203pmt", "aSentId": 364, "question": "Given that both sides know where they need to move, why the games?", "qSentId": 363}, {"answer": "Oh, yes, absolutely.", "docId": "121203pmt", "aSentId": 445, "question": "You're calling Reid as well?", "qSentId": 444}, {"answer": "Standing on the stage at the White House looking out at my buddies that I served in combat with, all the brass in the military, two families that had lost their sons that night that I was being awarded this medal for, it was very bittersweet.", "docId": "121203pmt", "aSentId": 479, "question": "How did you feel?", "qSentId": 478}, {"answer": "I absolutely love the Second Amendment.", "docId": "121203pmt", "aSentId": 549, "question": "What is your view about gun control in America?", "qSentId": 548}, {"answer": "Life's exciting.", "docId": "121203pmt", "aSentId": 558, "question": "What is life going to be like for you now?", "qSentId": 557}]